

POURNAMI KRISHNAN

DIGITAL DESIGNER
ASPIRING UI/UX DESIGNER

CONTACT

+46 729208071

POURNAMIKK@GMAIL.COM

WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/POURNAMIKK

SKILLS

USABILITY TESTING & DESIGN PROCESS
SKETCH
ADOBE PHOTOSHOP
WEB DESIGNING
MICROSOFT POWERPOINT
MICROSOFT WORD AND EXCEL
PROOF READING AND EDITING
WRITING AND REPORTING
MICROSOFT VISIO
WEB DEVELOPMENT

INTERESTS

DESIGN FOR ALL
DESIGN EVALUATION
USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNS
LAYOUT DESIGNS
RESEARCH
CONTENT WRITING & EDITING

PROFILE

Currently pursuing second year Masters in Human Computer Interaction and Design (EIT Program) at UPM, Madrid (Exit University) with first year at KTH, Sweden; specializing in Accessible and Adaptive Interaction. I am currently searching for job opportunities at a company where I can improve my knowledge and skills in the field of UI/UX Design, after the completion of my master thesis at RISE Viktoria (September).

EXPERIENCE

UX DESIGNER MASTER THESIS INTERN

RISE VIKTORIA, SWEDEN | FEBRUARY 2019 - JULY 2019

 Will work on the project about guidance to self-driving vehicles (cars and(or shuttle buses) for blind/deaf/deaf-blind persons using vibrotactile guidance.

UI/UX DESIGNER INTERN

DIGITALROUTE, SWEDEN | JUNE 2018 - AUGUST 2018

 Worked in a team of 3 to visualize spot price data from Amazon Web Services. Created a web interface for visually comparing pricings of different instances and regions for the DigitalRoute employees using usability testing and interviews during the design process.

BUSINESS ANALYST

CGI, INDIA | JANUARY 2017 - AUGUST 2017

 As a Business Analyst for the executives of the Shell Project, I was in charge of the content research and presenting the information effectively to the clients as well as internally.

BUSINESS PRESENTATION SPECIALIST DESIGNER MCKINSEY & CO., INDIA | SEPTEMBER 2014 - JULY 2016

- VGCS India, a wholly owned subsidiary of McKinsey & Company is engaged in the development of visual communication material like graphics, charts, exhibits, on-screen animated presentations, and multi-media products for McKinsey's global offices.
- As a BPD, I had to handle the urgent requirements of clients in a very tight deadline, producing top quality works.

EDUCATION

MASTERS IN HUMAN COMPUTER INTERACTION AND DESIGN UNIVERSIDAD POLITÉCNICA DE MADRID | 2018- PRESENT

 Currently pursuing my second year Masters as part of 2 year EIT Digital Masters Program at UPM, specializing in Accessible and Adaptive Interaction.

MASTERS IN HUMAN COMPUTER INTERACTION AND DESIGN KUNGLIGA TEKNISKA HÖGSKOLAN, SWEDEN | 2017-2018

Completed my first year Masters as part of 2 year EIT Digital Masters
Program at KTH. HCID focuses on the study, design, development and
evaluation of novel user interfaces, interactive systems and services.

BACHELOR OF ARTS IN MASS COMMUNICATION

AMRITA UNIVERSITY, INDIA | 2011-2014

 Majoring in Journalism and Digital Designing. 3 year course covering multidisciplinary topics like print journalism, visual communication, digital designing, radio, advertising, public relations, current affairs, photography and videography.